JORDIN KOLMAN

Python Developer

Hockley, TX 77447

jordinkolman@gmail.com

254-394-5535

Proficient in Python coding, both object oriented and class oriented, with a strong proficiency in back-end software and web development, and some experience with machine learning, data science, and website testing.

Also experienced with HTML5,CSS3, and JavaScript front-end web development, and React and Angular frameworks for JS

Developed a bot to automate Tinder to add to dating site experience, automatically swiping through potential matches and making a connection for the user.

Developed a website with a full python backend, showcasing other Python projects at jordinkolman.com.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer



WORK EXPERIENCE -----

Python/Web Developer

Freelance

March 2019 to Present

- Built a full-stack, deployed website with a Python back-end and HTML5/CSS3/JS front-end
- Built an application to test if passwords were compromised in a data breach, using UTF-8 encoding for security

Owner/Driver-Partner

JRK Transportation - Austin, TX

November 2015 to Present

- Minimized potential automotive accidents by providing over 3000 safe, reliable rides with no safety incidents using Uber and Lyft platforms
- Earned a 5 star rating from customers for all 4 years in service

Messenger/Driver

Brinks - Austin, TX

December 2017 to May 2018

• Lead a crew of 2-3 security couriers to efficiently transport currency and valuables with 0 safety issues or variances



EDUCATION

High school or equivalent in General

Waller High School - Waller, TX August 2009 to June 2013



SKILLS

- · Armed Security
- · Customer Service
- Security
- HTML5 (Less than 1 year)
- JavaScript (Less than 1 year)
- CSS3 (Less than 1 year)
- Python (Less than 1 year)
- HTML 5
- CSS
- Git
- APIs
- User Interface (UI)
- AWS
- React
- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- Angular



MILITARY SERVICE -----

Branch: United States Navy Service Country: United States

Rank: E-3(Seaman)

February 2017 to April 2017



CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

TABC

May 2016 to May 2018

Certified to serve alcohol and in safe alcohol serving practices

Commissioned Security License

February 2018 to February 2020

Licensed to carry a firearm in an official capacity for security services

Security Guard

Secret Security Clearance



ASSESSMENTS

First Aid Skills — Proficient

February 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to identify treatments for common medical emergencies.

Full results: Proficient

Problem Solving — Highly Proficient

February 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to analyze relevant information when solving problems.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Logic & Critical Thinking — Expert

February 2020

Using logic to solve problems.

Full results: Expert

Graphic Design — Familiar

October 2020

Using graphic design techniques and producing visual media to communicate concepts.

Full results: Familiar

Attention to Detail — Highly Proficient

October 2020

 $Identifying \ differences \ in \ materials, \ following \ instructions, \ and \ detecting \ details \ among \ distracting \ information.$

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.